Women's labour history interview collection (Sara Diamond interviewer)
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Women's labour history interview collection (Sara Diamond interviewer)
1978-2016, predominant 1978-1980
F-67
Q100361027
32 cm of textual records 43 sound recordings
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
PHYSICAL DESCRIPTION The original recordings were made on reel-to-reel audio tapes; for each interview, two additional copies were subsequently made on audiocassette. Audio cassettes were digitized to create .wav preservation copies.
Diamond, Sara
published
Full
Revised
Title of the collection is based on the contents.
The Women's Labour History Project documents the histories of women who were active in the trade union movement in British Columbia from 1890s onwards. The project was initiated by Sara Diamond, an undergraduate history student at SFU, who conducted the interviews. She received financial support from the British Columbia Summer Youth Employment Fund. Additional funding was received from many other sources, including The Canada Council, and the Federal Department of Human Resources. Diamond provides a description of her research methodology in a report included as Appendix A1, "Women's Labour History Project" (available in the hard-copy finding aid only).
The collection consists of 43 interviews conducted by Sara Diamond with women in the labour movement in British Columbia. The women discuss their childhoods, family lives, careers, social issues such as childcare and birth control, economic situations such as the depresssion and post-war employment, and the working conditions that led them to become union activists. A summary of each interview is provided in Appendix 1, "Women's Labour History Project" (available in hard-copy finding aid only).
The collection contains audio recordings and transcripts.
The arrangement of the material was provided by the archivist. Originally transcripts and the audio recordings were included in the same series; in September 2010, the archivist moved the audio recordings into a separate series and re-assigned item numbers.
Sound recordings; Textual records; Records in electronic form (digitized); Labour; Women
The audio interviews and transcripts were donated by Sara Diamond. Material in the appendices was added by the archivist. Note that one transcript (for the Pearl Wong Moreau interview, file F-67-1-0-0-25) was created in 2016 by a researcher (Robin Folvik) from the audio recording and donated to the Archives.
All accessions have been processed as of September 2002. No further accruals are expected.
There are no restrictions on the materials. Access to the sound recordings is normally provided via the copies on cassette. For some interviews, a digital copy made be available; consult the reference archivist for more details.
Lists of the audio recordings and transcripts are available. Summaries of the interviews and Diamond's report on the history of the project, a bibliography, and an article by Diamond on women in the labour movement are available in the hard copy version of the finding aid maintained in the Archives Reading Room.
- Interviews: transcripts, 1979; F-67-1; 32 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of transcripts of the interviews.
  Arrangement provided by the archivist; each interview has its own file.
  There are no restrictions on access.
  - Andersen, Anita interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Andersen, Anita; Textual records
    Open
  - Arthur, Anna interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Arthur, Anna; Textual records
  - Atkinson, Jack interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Atkinson, Jack; Textual records
  - Barber, Ellen interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Barber, Ellen; Textual records
  - Bergren, Myrtle interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Bergren, Myrtle; Textual records
  - Brown, Daisy interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Brown, Daisy; Textual records
  - Bullock, Ruth interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Bullock, Ruth; Textual records
  - Charlie, Josephine interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Charlie, Josephine; Textual records
  - Dowding, Vivian interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Vivian Dowding; Textual records
  - Fawcett, Suzie interview [no transcript], 1979; F-67-1-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Suzie Fawcett; Textual records
  - Foster, Buster interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Foster, Buster; Textual records
  - Gillatt, Joan interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Gillatt, Joan; Textual records
  - Godkin, Thelma interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Godkin, Thelma; Textual records
  - Hallock, Josephine interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Hallock, Josephine; Textual records
  - Hilland, Gladys interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Hilland, Gladys; Textual records
  - Jones, Effie interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Jones, Effie; Textual records
  - Judd, Janet interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Judd, Janet Joyce; Textual records
  - Kennedy, Peggy interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 67-1)
    Kennedy, Peggy; Textual records
  - Lake Cowichan Women's Auxiliary interview [Eva Wilson, et al], 1979; F-67-1-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    Lake Cowichan Women's Auxiliary; Textual records
  - Ledger, Verna interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    Ledger, Verna; Textual records
  - Marshall, Anne interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    Marshall, Anne; Textual records
  - Martin, May interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    Martin, May; Textual records
  - McKinnon, Sara interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    McKinnon, Sara; Textual records
  - McLeod, Edra interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    McLeod, Edra; Textual records
  - Moreau, Pearl Wong interview, 2016; 1979; F-67-1-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    Moreau, Pearl; Textual records
  - Morrison, Jim interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    Morrison, Jim; Textual records
  - Nuttall, Emily interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    Nuttall, Emily; Textual records
  - Ouellette, Jeanne interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    Ouellette, Jeanne; Textual records
  - Overgaard, Muriel interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    Overgaard, Muriel; Textual records
  - Person, Alice interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    Person, Alice; Textual records
  - Rankin, Jonnie interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    Rankin, Jonnie; Textual records
  - Sarich, Marion interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    Sarich, Marion; Textual records
  - Scott, Jean interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    Scott, Jean; Textual records
  - Souderholm, Bertha interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 67-2)
    Souderholm, Bertha; Textual records
  - Stewart, Barbara interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-35 (Archival box - small 67-3)
    Stewart, Barbara; Textual records
  - Stoneman, Lil interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-36 (Archival box - small 67-3)
    Stoneman, Lil; Textual records
  - Storm, Marjorie interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-37 (Archival box - small 67-3)
    Storm, Marjorie; Textual records
  - Tallman, Eileen interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-38 (Archival box - small 67-3)
    Tallman, Eileen; Textual records
  - Vaselenek, Eva interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-39 (Archival box - small 67-3)
    Vaselenek, Eva; Textual records
  - Waddell, Chris interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-40 (Archival box - small 67-3)
    Waddell, Chris; Textual records
  - Whisker, Richard and Phyllis interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-41 (Archival box - small 67-3)
    Whisker, Phyllis; Whisker, Richard; Textual records
  - White, Bill interview [White, Connie interview no tape], 1979; F-67-1-0-0-42 (Archival box - small 67-3)
    White, Bill; Textual records
  - Wilson, Elizabeth (Liz) interview, 1979; F-67-1-0-0-43 (Archival box - small 67-3)
    Wilson, Elizabeth; Textual records
- Interviews: sound recordings, 1979; F-67-2; 43 sound recordings
  Series consists of audio recordings of the interviews.
  Arrangement provided by the archivist. Each interview has been assigned an item number; note that some interviews may have several parts (run over more than one reel or tape).
  Access to the original reel-to-reel and cassette recordings is restricted due to the fragility of the medium. Access is provided via digitized reproductions of the audio cassettes.
  - Andersen, Anita, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-1; 1 sound recording (Audio cassette OBJ-609, Audio cassette OBJ-610, Audio reel OBJ-680, Audio reel OBJ-681)
    Andersen, Anita; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    .wav files also available in .mp3 format.
    Sound recording available on:
    2 audio reels
    2 audio cassettes
    4 .wav files
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item1, F-67-item2, F-67-item85, F-67-item86.
    - OBJ-609_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-609_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-610_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-610_sideB.wav
  - Arthur, Anna, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-2; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-682, Audio reel OBJ-683, Audio cassette OBJ-611, Audio cassette OBJ-612)
    Arthur, Anna; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Sound recording contained on:
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item3, F-67-item4, F-67-item87, F-67-item88.
    - OBJ-611_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-611_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-612_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-612_sideB.wav
  - Atkinson, Jack, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-3; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-684, Audio cassette OBJ-613)
    Atkinson, Jack; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    1 audio reel
    1 audio cassette
    2 .wav files
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item5, F-67-item89.
    - OBJ-613_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-613_sideB.wav
  - Barber, Ellen, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-4; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-685, Audio reel OBJ-686, Audio reel OBJ-687, Audio cassette OBJ-614, Audio cassette OBJ-615)
    Barber, Ellen; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    3 audio reels
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item6, F-67-item7, F-67-item8, F-67-item90, F-67-item91.
    - OBJ-614_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-614_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-615_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-615_sideB.wav
  - Bergren, Myrtle, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-5; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-688, Audio reel OBJ-689, Audio cassette OBJ-616, Audio cassette OBJ-617)
    Bergren, Myrtle; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item9, F-67-item10, F-67-item92, F-67-item93.
    - OBJ-616_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-616_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-617_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-617_sideB.wav
  - Brown, Daisy, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-6; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-690, Audio reel OBJ-691, Audio cassette OBJ-618)
    Brown, Daisy; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item11, F-67-item12, F-67-item94.
    - OBJ-618_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-618_sideB.wav
  - Bullock, Ruth, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-7; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-692, Audio reel OBJ-693, Audio cassette OBJ-619, Audio cassette OBJ-620, Audio cassette OBJ-621, Audio cassette OBJ-622)
    Bullock, Ruth; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    4 audio cassettes
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item13, F-67-item14, F-67-item95, F-67-item96, F-67-item97, F-67-item98.
    - OBJ-619_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-619_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-620_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-620_sideB.wav
  - Charlie, Josephine, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-8; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-694, Audio reel OBJ-695, Audio reel OBJ-696, Audio cassette OBJ-623, Audio cassette OBJ-624)
    Charlie, Josephine; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item15, F-67-item16, F-67-item17, F-67-item99, F-67-item100.
    - OBJ-623_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-623_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-624_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-624_sideB.wav
  - Dowding, Vivian, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-9; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-697, Audio cassette OBJ-625, Audio cassette OBJ-626)
    Vivian Dowding; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    OBJ-626 is an exact copy of OBJ-625.
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item18, F-67-item102.
    - OBJ-625_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-625_sideB.wav
  - Fawcett, Suzie, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-10; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-698, Audio cassette OBJ-627)
    Suzie Fawcett; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item19, F-67-item103.
    - OBJ-627_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-627_sideB.wav
  - Foster, Buster, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-11; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-699, Audio reel OBJ-700, Audio cassette OBJ-628, Audio cassette OBJ-629)
    Foster, Buster; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item20, F-67-item21, F-67-item104, F-67-item105.
    - OBJ-628_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-628_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-629_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-629_sideB.wav
  - Gillatt, Joan, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-12; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-701, Audio reel OBJ-702, Audio cassette OBJ-630)
    Gillatt, Joan; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    .wav files also available in .mp4.
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item22, F-67-item23, F-67-item106.
    - OBJ-630_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-630_sideB.wav
  - Godkin, Thelma, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-13; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-703, Audio cassette OBJ-631, Optical disc: cd OBJ-3980, Optical disc: cd-r OBJ-3981, Optical disc: cd-r OBJ-3982, Webdav: virtual stacks OBJ-4020)
    Godkin, Thelma; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    3 optical discs
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item24, F-67-item107.
    - OBJ-631_SideA.wav
    - OBJ-631_SideB.wav
  - Hallock, Josephine, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-14; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-704, Audio reel OBJ-705, Audio cassette OBJ-632, Audio cassette OBJ-633)
    Hallock, Josephine; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item25, F-67-item26, F-67-item108, F-67-item109.
    - OBJ-632_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-632_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-633_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-633_sideB.wav
  - Hilland, Gladys, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-15; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-706, Audio reel OBJ-707, Audio reel OBJ-708, Audio cassette OBJ-634, Audio cassette OBJ-635)
    Hilland, Gladys; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item27, F-67-item28, F-67-item29, F-67-item110, F-67-item111.
    - OBJ-634_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-634_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-635_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-635_sideB.wav
  - Jones, Effie, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-16; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-709, Audio reel OBJ-710, Audio reel OBJ-711, Audio cassette OBJ-636, Audio cassette OBJ-637)
    Jones, Effie; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item30, F-67-item31, F-67-item32, F-67-item112, F-67-item113.
    - OBJ-636_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-636_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-637_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-637_sideB.wav
  - Judd, Janet Joyce, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-17; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-712, Audio reel OBJ-713, Audio cassette OBJ-638)
    Judd, Janet Joyce; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    1 .wav files
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item33, F-67-item34, F-67-item113.
    - OBJ-638_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-638_sideB.wav
  - Kennedy, Peggy, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-18; 2 audio reels 1 audio cassette 2 wav files (Audio reel OBJ-714, Audio reel OBJ-715, Audio cassette OBJ-639)
    Kennedy, Peggy; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item35, F-67-item36, F-67-item115.
    - OBJ-639_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-639_sideB.wav
  - Lake Cowichan Women's Auxiliary, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-19; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-752, Audio reel OBJ-753, Audio reel OBJ-754, Audio cassette OBJ-640, Audio cassette OBJ-641)
    Wilson, Eva; Godfrey, Lillian; Lake Cowichan Women's Auxiliary; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item37, F-67-item38, F-67-item39, F-67-item116, F-67-item117.
    - OBJ-641_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-641_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-640_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-640_sideB.wav
  - Ledger, Verna, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-20; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-755, Audio cassette OBJ-642)
    Ledger, Verna; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    1 sound recording contained on:
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item40, F-67-item118.
    - OBJ-642_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-642_sideB.wav
  - Marshall, Anne, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-21; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-756, Audio reel OBJ-757, Audio cassette OBJ-643)
    Marshall, Anne; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item41, F-67-item42, F-67-item119.
    - OBJ-643_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-643_sideB.wav
  - Martin, May, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-22; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-716, Audio reel OBJ-717, Audio reel OBJ-718, Audio cassette OBJ-644, Audio cassette OBJ-645)
    Martin, May; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item43, F-67-item44, F-67-item45, F-67-item120, F-67-item121.
    - OBJ-644_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-644_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-645_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-645_sideB.wav
  - McKinnon, Sara, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-23; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-719, Audio reel OBJ-720, Audio cassette OBJ-660, Audio cassette OBJ-661)
    McKinnon, Sara; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item46, F-67-item47, F-67-item122, F-67-item123.
    - OBJ-660_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-660_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-661_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-661_sideB.wav
  - McLeod, Edra, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-24; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-721, Audio reel OBJ-722, Audio cassette OBJ-646, Audio cassette OBJ-647)
    McLeod, Edra; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item48, F-67-item49, F-67-item124, F-67-item125.
    - OBJ-646_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-646_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-647_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-647_sideB.wav
  - Moreau, Pearl [Pearl Wong], 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-25; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-723, Audio cassette OBJ-649)
    Moreau, Pearl; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item50, F-67-item126.
    - OBJ-649_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-649_sideB.wav
  - Morrison, Jim, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-26; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-724, Audio cassette OBJ-648)
    Morrison, Jim; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item51, F-67-item127.
    - OBJ-648_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-648_sideB.wav
  - Nuttall, Emily, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-27; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-725, Audio reel OBJ-726, Audio cassette OBJ-650, Audio cassette OBJ-651)
    Nuttall, Emily; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item52, F-67-item53, F-67-item128, F-67-item129.
    - OBJ-650_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-650_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-651_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-651_sideB.wav
  - Ouellette, Jeanne, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-28; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-727, Audio cassette OBJ-652)
    Ouellette, Jeanne; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    .wav file also available in .mp3 format.
    1 .wav file
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item54, F-67-item130.
    - OBJ-652_sideA.wav
  - Overgaard, Muriel, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-29; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-728, Audio reel OBJ-729, Audio cassette OBJ-653)
    Overgaard, Muriel; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item55, F-67-item56, F-67-item131.
    - OBJ-653_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-653_sideB.wav
  - Person, Alice, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-30; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-730, Audio reel OBJ-731, Audio cassette OBJ-654)
    Person, Alice; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item57, F-67-item58, F-67-item132.
    - OBJ-654_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-654_sideB.wav
  - Rankin, Jonnie, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-31; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-732, Audio reel OBJ-733, Audio cassette OBJ-655, Audio cassette OBJ-656)
    Rankin, Jonnie; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item59, F-67-item60, F-67-item133, F-67-item134.
    - OBJ-655_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-655_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-656_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-656_sideB.wav
  - Sarich, Marion, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-32; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-734, Audio reel OBJ-735, Audio reel OBJ-736, Audio cassette OBJ-657, Audio cassette OBJ-658)
    Sarich, Marion; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item61, F-67-item62, F-67-item63, F-67-item135, F-67-item136.
    - OBJ-657_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-657_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-658_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-658_sideB.wav
  - Scott, Jean, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-33; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-737, Audio reel OBJ-738, Audio cassette OBJ-659)
    Scott, Jean; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item64, F-67-item65, F-67-item137.
    - OBJ-659_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-659_sideB.wav
  - Souderholm, Bertha, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-34 (Audio reel OBJ-739, Audio cassette OBJ-662)
    Souderholm, Bertha; Sound recordings
    Duration: 0
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item66, F-67-item138.
    - OBJ-662_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-662_sideB.wav
  - Stewart, Barbara, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-35 (Audio reel OBJ-740, Audio reel OBJ-741, Audio cassette OBJ-663, Audio cassette OBJ-664)
    Stewart, Barbara; Sound recordings
    Duration: 2
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item67, F-67-item68, F-67-item139, F-67-item140.
    - OBJ-663_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-663_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-664_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-664_sideB.wav
  - Stoneman, Lil, 1979; F-67-2-0-0-0-36; 1 sound recording (Audio reel OBJ-742, Audio reel OBJ-743, Audio reel OBJ-744, Audio cassette OBJ-665, Audio cassette OBJ-666)
    Stoneman, Lil; Sound recordings; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-67-item69, F-67-item70, F-67-item71, F-67-item141, F-67-item142.
    - OBJ-665_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-665_sideB.wav
    - OBJ-666_sideA.wav
    - OBJ-666_sideB.wav